Maximilian H. Orozco

Front-end Web Developer

(213) 369-8412 · maxorozco213@gmail.com www.github.com/maxorozco213/ www.linkedin.com/in/maximilian-h-orozco/

EDUCATION

California State University, Los Angeles Bachelor of Science, Computer Science Graduated May 2020

San Francisco State University

Bachelor of Science, Computer Science

August 2014 - May 2017

SUMMARY

Dedicated and quick-learning front-end software developer with 4+ years of experience in computer science and 2+ years of experience in UX design for various projects. Experience in building web applications with JavaScript and ReactJS with the use of related web technologies like Redux, Docker, HTML, and CSS. Strong programming skills in Python. Excellent communication and team collaboration skills.

EXPERIENCE

Buelna News Blog

February 2020 - August 2020

Project Lead (JavaScript, Python/Django)

- Led weekly meetings with the team members and periodic meetings with the client
- Tracked all members' tasks and assigned deadlines
- Designed and implemented a full-stack web application to allow post sharing and editing
- Created **Docker** containers for all modules
- Deployed the application on AWS EC2 servers with HTTPS certificates

Boeing August 2019 – May 2020

Senior Design Student (JavaScript, Python/Django)

- Designed and implemented a full-stack web application to gather and analyze satellite telemetry
- · Designed the application to display thousands of data points analyzed with machine learning
- Containerized application modules using Docker
- Authored descriptive and thorough documentation of the project
- Deployed the application for public access on AWS EC2 servers

Alpha Phi Omega Mobile Application

React Native Developer

May 2018 – December 2018

- Participated in weekly **SCRUM** meetings
- Assisted in the development of a mobile app to be used by thousands across the country
- Integrated the existing API with the new application
- Exhaustively tested and debugged the existing code base

EXTRACURRICULARS

SFSU/CSULA Alpha Phi Omega

February 2015 - May 2020

Active Organization Member, Former Secretary, Former Sergeant-At-Arms

- Participated in a large variety of volunteer/community service projects
- Achieved elected positions as Sergeant-At-Arms (2016) and Secretary (2018)
- Created templates for more efficient, long-term record keeping
- Managed, updated, and upheld chapter bylaws

AWARDS

- Selected from a candidate pool of over 100 applicants to receive a scholarship from Metal Services Center Institute (MSCI) for academic achievement and involvement in extracurricular activities
- Received the Dean's List acknowledgement for academic achievement at SFSU